sci-news.com 2012-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Sci-News.com

> Sci-News.com is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. To better inform you of our policy concerning user privacy, we have adopted the following terms. Please note that these terms are subject to change, and any such changes will be included on this page.
> 
>  **Information that Sci-News.com May Collect Online**
> 
> Sci-News.com may collect and process the following data about you:
> 
> \- information that you provide by filling in forms on our site, including names, e-mail and website addresses; we may also ask you for information for other purposes, for example when you report a problem with our site;
> 
> \- if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence;
> 
> \- details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data.
> 
> Sci-News.com does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. We assume that minors 13 years of age or older have received permission from their parents or guardians before using this website. Parents or guardians may contact us at [privacy@sci-news.com](mailto:privacy@sci-news.com) with questions or concerns about our privacy policy.
> 
>  **Use of Cookies**
> 
> Sci-News.com uses “cookie” technology. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes a unique identifier that is sent to your computer or mobile phone browser from a website’s computer and is stored on your device’s hard drive. A website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other websites. Many websites do this whenever a user visits their website in order to track online traffic flows.
> 
> During the course of any visit to the Sci-News.com website, the pages you see, along with a cookie, are downloaded to your device. A website does this because cookies enable a publisher to find out whether the device has visited the website before. This is done on a repeat visit by checking to see, and finding, the cookie left there on the last visit.
> 
> Please note that during or after your visits to the Sci-News.com website you may notice some cookies that are not related to it. Sci-News.com does not control the dissemination of these cookies. You must check the third party websites for more information about these.
> 
> You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the site.
> 
>  **Disclosure of Your Information**
> 
> Sci-News.com does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties. If we choose to do so in the future, you will be notified by email of our intentions, and have the right to be removed prior to the disclosure.
> 
>  **Your Consent and Rights**
> 
> By using Sci-News.com, you consent to the collection and use, in accordance with this policy, of the information you provide to us.
> 
> We will remove you and your personally identifiable information from our records on request if you contact us with your request at [privacy@sci-news.com](mailto:privacy@sci-news.com).
> 
>  **Contact Us**
> 
> If you have any inquiries about this Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us at [privacy@sci-news.com](mailto:privacy@sci-news.com).
